You know, boys join French classes
to flirt with girls.
But our boy Gautam
actually went there to study French.
[speaking French]
"Which platform does
the train leave from?"
[speaking French]
Hi.
-Hi.
-Any problem?
No, why?
You're cussing so profusely,
I thought something is bothering you.
Oh, no, no, I was just practising.
Okay.
I feel one should know
how to cuss in every language.
[cussing in French]
Helps in getting rid
of the loafers, you see.
Free advice.
-She's perfect for him.
-I swear.
She's bound to bring
some fun into his life.
What about you?
What about me?
Why are you learning French?
I work for the IFS,
Indian Foreign Services.
I thought they'd send me to Europe
if I have French on my resume.
Okay.
Yeah, that's the plan.
Yeah.
Oh, so you're the guy who plans.
Why? Is that a crime?
No, no, no!
Me, no plan. Never.
You know he's so bad at flirting,
he always ends up
getting friend-zoned.
Want to go out with me for coffee?
Actually, scratch that,
want to go out with me for dinner?
Sure.
Is this invitation only for me,
or is it extended to my boyfriend,
Ketan, as well?
[speaking French]
But when they are together,
they are so good.
Did we see this day coming?
Not even in our dreams.
"My beloved is my wealth"
"My beloved is my downfall"
"The love we share
Bears witness to that"
"My beloved is my wealth"
"My beloved is my downfall"
"The love we share
Bears witness to that"
"You are the reason"
"I am the happiest man
In the world"
"Oh, God
I couldn't have asked for me"
"My love"
"I pray for your long life"
"I want you to be
My lawfully wedded wife"
"My darling"
"I pray for your long life"
"I want you to be
My lawfully wedded wife"
"May you be blessed
With prosperity"
"May you always keep glowing
With happiness"
"May your bangles never lose shine"
"May God keep you away from evil"
-This is such a sissy drink.
-I don't want a cold drink.
-Vodka, please.
-Give me the expensive stuff.
The most expensive one.
-Double large.
-Fill it to the brim.
Excuse me, everyone.
-Can I have your attention, please?
-Black. Black.
-Double black.
-A glass of Black as well.
Actually, all the men in my family
believe in romance.
You know, they are really romantic.
In 1949, a gypsy lady showed
my grandpa a simple ring
-in a Turkish market and said...
-You're interested in his speech?
..."It's a ruh muska.
"You know, it's a soul compass?
"Any man in possession of this ring
will meet his dream girl."
Yes, she said that.
You're listening to this,
seriously?
In 1977,
Grandma gave that ring to Dad.
Back then, Dad was
posted in Singapore.
That's where he met my mom, Sona.
So, it was really working.
We'll get caught.
-About a year ago...
-It's expensive stuff. Stop it, Pinky.
-...my mom gave me that ring...
-We'll get caught.
...and said, "Gautam, this ring
really works. It's really magical."
At that point, I thought
mom was just really being silly.
But...
one day...
like a breath of fresh air,
I meet a girl.
That's the day I realised...
that this ring has
still not lost its magic.
Ira.
This ring has your name written
all over it.
Would you do me
the honour of wearing it?
Clap, guys.
Ira, if we hadn't met in London,
we would've met in Paris.
If not Paris, then Amsterdam.
Ira, I'd have found you
in any corner of the world,
be it a village, town or city...
because you are my destiny.
I really love you, Ira.
I love you too, Gautam.
Can I have some ice, bro?
What do you want to drink, Jaggi?
Well said, bro! Superb!
-Shush, it's a biggie's wedding.
-Well said, bro.
-What are you doing, Jaggi?
-Give me a second. Bro, you've...
-He'll get us killed. Bloody idiot.
-Look over there.
You've touched my heart, bro.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you so much.
You are one lucky girl.
He's a gem of a person.
That's okay.
You don't need to do this.
I usually don't have
more than one drink, bro.
But since this is a family wedding,
with your permission,
may I have one more?
Sure, please.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you so much.
Bye. Enjoy.
Sure.
Funny guy.
You didn't introduce us, Ira.
I thought he's one
of your relatives.
I'll just go and check.
Look, Mr. Chaudhary,
this is the kind of love I seek.
There's something called
as Double Black as well?
-Let me drink.
-Will you...
One should love, marry
and grow old with the same woman.
-What's going on?
-I'm in love with four.
-No! This is wrong.
-God knows.
-I love every girl I see.
-Excuse me?
Excuse me?
Whose side are you from?
Me? I am from my side.
His side!
But...
I am Jaggi, Joginder.
-This is Rane. That's Pinky.
-Nice wedding.
You guys think that's funny?
Who invited you guys?
-We--
-God invites us all into this world.
What can we do?
What can we do
but enjoy our drinks!
He is drunk, bro.
He's a lightweight.
Whom are you calling, sir?
You all will get sober
once the police get here.
Police!
Calling the police
won't do you any good, bro.
Who will be on duty at this hour?
-Bhishma.
Bro, if Bhishma comes here,
I'll want four bottles from you.
-We just need one.
-He's a drunk, bro.
Where's the organiser?
There's a boy's hostel
next door, sir.
They gatecrash every wedding.
-Hey!
-Please keep quiet.
-I gave you 500 bucks.
-Buzz off before I smash your face.
Sorry, bro.
Sorry. I apologise.
Don't let this ruin your mood.
It's your wedding.
You gave such a beautiful
speech for your wife.
As far as compensating
for these drinks is concerned,
you can come to my wedding
and have as many drinks as you want.
Imported liquor.
-Just get them out of this place.
-Please leave.
-This is... imported liquor.
-Come on.
-You are invited as well. Promise.
-We are leaving.
Don't touch. Don't touch!
Come on, let's just go back now.
Hey! I am Pinky Singh.
I'll see you outside.
I'll hit you with a hockey stick.
"I'd find you from
any corner of the world.
"If we hadn't met in the village,
we would've met in the city.
"If not Ludhiana then Bathinda,
Amritsar, Sangrur,
"Gujarat, Kerala
or someplace else...
"because you are my destiny."
What he said is just perfect.
Bang on target.
His kick was also perfect,
bang on target.
-Ruined the mood.
-Where can we find some ice, bro?
-Ruined the high.
-Someone please find me some ice.
This was the first time
I had expensive liquor.
You.
Throw passport, IDs, come on.
Nazir...
[in Pashto] Check him properly.
His clothes too.
Remove it.
You have a tag here as well.
Throw that as well.
What are you doing?
Remove that as well.
Listen,
get rid of anything that
will tell them where you are from.
This doesn't tell anything.
Just fold it and
hide it in your shoes.
Your family sent you here
all by yourself?
There is no one else left.
The bombings...
razed everything to the ground.
What will you do in London?
My cousin lives there.
Really?
In London?
How did he get there?
He went there five years ago,
holding on to a plane's tyre.
It's not as easy as holding
on to a cycle or a bus's tyre.
Planes tyres retract after take-off.
I know.
There is some space
next to the tyre.
That's where he hid.
He was almost frozen to death,
but he's okay now.
He works in a restaurant.
He told me that
he'll help me get settled there.
Where are you going?
London.
Do you too have someone there?
Yes, I do.
I'll surely introduce them
to you one day.
You can treat us
in your restaurant.
Light off.
Now check post.
Border.
When I press horn,
you wear this over head.
Okay.
-No breathing.
-Okay.
Checking machine.
Machine, yeah?
Checking.
If you get caught,
I don't know you.
Okay?
I can't do this.
Hey, it's nothing, Bilal.
I cannot do it.
Bilal, it will only
take two minutes, okay?
Once we cross the border
and enter UK,
you will get to
be with your brother.
Right?
[speaking French]
Don't move!
Freeze!
Don't move! Hands up! Don't move!
Don't shoot!
No.
Bonjour.
-[speaking French]
-Sir. Sir, please.
-Please, sir. I want to...
Sir, help.
Help. Help.
-Bonjour, Gautam.
-Bonjour.
They've been well-coached.
No identification.
Refuse to say a word
except "asylum."
Qadri has figured
his Pakistani lot out.
Would really appreciate if you
could check your Indian illegals.
Yes.
What village are you from?
What is your father's name?
Asylum.
What is your mother's name?
[speaking Pashto]
-Asylum.
-[speaking Arabic]
Hello?
[speaking Arabic]
Asylum.
You are definitely not
from Afghanistan or Syria.
Where are you from?
India? Pakistan? Bangladesh?
Asylum.
Asy...
They are professionals.
Get their blood test done.
-Bro?
-Sure.
Bro!
Bro, it's me, Jaggi.
We won't be able to help them.
Remember me? I had gatecrashed
your wedding, caused a ruckus?
[speaking French]
They'll need to...
Come on, man!
"If not here, then there.
"Bathinda, Sangrur...
"London, Amsterdam?"
It's me.
So...
You have a habit of
going to places uninvited.
You are making India proud.
Everyone has the same story.
Score low grades in school.
Drop out from college.
Gatecrash weddings.
Free booze.
Then start believing your family
and friends don't get you.
"Let's go to the United States
of America.
"United Kingdom."
Easy money, huh?
No, bro, you misunderstand.
It's not so.
Let me tell you something.
To pay for high school,
I used to sell tea and biscuits at
a small railway station in Punjab.
Of course without having
the necessary permits.
Station Master Roshanlal
used to say,
"Jaggi, you make tea better
than those with permits."
My tea used to get sold out
even before the evening train
would hit the station.
I used to make 500 bucks every day.
I could have made easy money
there itself.
What an incredible achievement!
So, you have crossed the borders
of eight nations to sell tea?
Or to clean the toilets of Europe?
Look, I meet losers
like you every day.
No, bro, I am sure you have
never come across anyone like me.
Bro, I am actually here
because of what you said.
And as if fate had planned this,
I found you here.
Because of what I said?
Yes!
Hey nice, Jaggi.
-Jaggi! Jaggi! Jaggi!
-What?
Come here.
-You know what I saw?
-What?
Mermaids in the swimming pool.
Trust me, beautiful fair-skinned
girls swimming in skimpy costumes.
-Let's go enjoy the view, pretty please?
-You get so excited over little things.
Please, let's go
and enjoy the view.
-It will be fun.
-Let's focus on the game.
You want to focus on the game?
If we play well here, we'll have
a fixed spot in the Indian camp
Two years of hard work and
we could be international players.
We'll be stars.
Parties, night clubs,
beautiful babes--
This isn't cricket
that you'll become a star.
You are a hockey player.
What makes you think there'll be
parties, night clubs and babes?
Have you lost your mind?
At the most,
you'll get a decent job
in the army or the railways,
thanks to the sports quota.
Right. And you will get surely get to
see girls but at the railway station.
Where you'll be
wearing a black coat,
and holding a red flag in one hand
and a green flag in the other.
He's talking nonsense.
You are right.
Jaggi, we should go enjoy the view.
Right? Let's get going immediately
without wasting another minute.
Yes, let's leave
before the coach comes.
-Let's go, let's go, let's go.
-Hey, we'll be right back.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Take your mark.
They are quite fit.
No one's wearing a two-piece, dude!
I think I am in fairyland.
Control your lust, boys.
It should look like
you do this every day.
Look natural. Just...
You're in sportswear, you fools.
Put your feet down.
Come on!
Look natural.
This is natural for me, Jaggi.
I have spent my childhood
in the lake with the buffalos.
This is making my eyes well up.
Think beyond the buffaloes, Pinky.
Act like a dude.
They are fit.
Amazing.
That's one beautiful mermaid.
Where?
Damn, girl.
Jaggi?
She is so beautiful.
She is indeed a mermaid.
The one in pink?
She is coming this way.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Oh.
Pinky!
Click a nice pic with her
in the background.
Have you lost your mind?
You'll get us killed.
Take this, duffer.
-It's just a photo.
-My followers will die of jealousy.
Come on.
She is coming this way.
-Take a pose.
-Done.
She's here.
Hurry up.
Done.
One more. Ready.
-Did you click it?
-Come on.
One more. Change.
-Done. I clicked it.
-Done?
Done?
-How is it?
-It's good.
Why were you flipping us the bird?
How is it?
Good enough for me.
We can try again if you want.
Sure.
You want me to go back in,
come out, give a Baywatch pose?
No, you don't need to go back in.
You can walk through here again.
That would do the job.
Trust me,
it will break the Internet.
What's going on?
You clicked my picture
without my permission.
And you plan to post it?
What's your name?
Joginder Dhillon.
But I go by Jaggi Dil
on social media.
Joginder Dhillon.
That's a better choice
for court, right?
Perfect.
-Court?
-Her dad will sue you in London.
Oh, I pity the state
you'll end up in.
Not worth it, dude.
Delete the picture.
Don't post it even by mistake.
Do it now.
-By the way...
-Do it.
...where do you get condoms
your size?
Excuse me?
Because you're the biggest
dick I've seen, dude.
Good one.
They your lackeys? Cute.
Why? Do you want to
have lunch with them?
Ignore her.
We'll find another mermaid.
I can't ignore her, dude.
She just challenged me that
too in her high-class English.
I will have to post it,
Mr. Chaudhary.
What's that all about?
Hey, nice pic, babe.
Babe?
What an idiot!
Stop it.
Hello, boys.
-Hey, hey, hey!
-Relax.
Who let them in?
-Damn it! Jaggi!
-Stop hiding. Give me that.
You don't need that towel.
-Who let them in?
-Turn around, princess.
Where is Jaspreet?
-Jaspreet!
-Hi.
This is not right.
-You enjoy watching naked men?
-Not fair.
They don't act this shy
when they keep staring at us.
-Exactly.
-No, no, no!
We feel shy.
Damn it!
This is not fair.
-What is going on?
-Not fair.
Why are you feeling shy now?
Don't take the bag.
I'm warning you.
I'll file a complaint against you.
Disappointing.
I'll...
-Hey!
-You really need to stay without that.
No! Ma!
There you are.
You want to click my pictures?
Well, it's time to see
your Baywatch pose now.
Do it right, then.
Wait a second.
-Here.
-Cool.
Sure. Okay.
Okay.
Hey, GQ. The GQ pose.
Come on, darling.
You'll run out of battery
before I run out of poses.
Keep clicking.
Can you call Sunita
from the archery team?
She should meet him.
She'll shoot the arrow
in such a place--
That you'll have to take showers
in the girls' locker room.
Really?
Then we'll get to meet every day.
Right?
Hey, what's wrong?
Fine. Don't forget
to share the pictures.
I don't have
any shirtless pictures anyway.
There is a great restaurant nearby.
Let's go there and gorge.
You can eat whatever you want.
You are not going to get
any medals anyway.
You might as well eat
to your heart's content.
Look at your timings.
Niharika: 1 minute 11 seconds.
Anushka: 1 minute 13 seconds.
Kartika: 1 minute 6 seconds.
And Sheena: 1 minute 7 seconds.
Have you seen the timings
of those girls from Bengal?
1.2.
What is going on?
Are you here to pass time?
Dismissed. Go!
I'll practise more, sir.
Yeah. Fine.
Thank God. Babe, I gotta pee.
I'll see you later.
Not now.
Why don't you go and
watch some porn instead?
Excuse me!
I'm just here to say...
No use showing me your finger.
I am not going to put a ring on it.
I know you've seen me naked,
but we hardly know each other.
Shameless.
I'll be damned.
You won't leave?
Cool. Be of some use.
Stopwatch's in the bag.
Time me.
Show.
-Yeah?
-Show.
Shit.
Still 2.25 seconds behind.
This is very bad.
How can you possibly
get any better by tomorrow?
Thanks.
I have a solution.
You are overweight.
You should reduce some weight.
Sorry?
What the hell did you just say?
You are overweight.
Asshole!
-Fucker!
-Loser!
-Loafer!
-Wait a second.
Why are you cussing him?
Just, man, moral support.
By the way, what did I miss?
I am in no mood to practise today.
-My stomach's upset.
-Why? What did you eat?
Storm's approaching, Jaggi!
-Huh?
-Storm.
Want me to join you?
Babe, I am here if you need me.
How dare you!
How dare I what?
How dare you say that!
What? Oh!
About you being overweight?
You are overweight by 300 kilos.
300 kilos?
-What... what do you mean?
-What... what...
Manipur's burdening this shoulder.
Kerala burdening that one.
Oh, you are carrying Punjab
and Bengal on your back.
Tell me something, how do you
manage to swim with all this burden?
What do you mean?
What?
Look, it's quite simple.
This isn't a mathematics
or statistics class.
0.3, 1.5, 2.9, so on and so forth.
Your only job when you are
in water is to enjoy swimming.
Look, you used to swim well
because you were happy in water.
You used to enjoy swimming.
I am a good player
because I enjoy hockey.
Forget the pressure,
the worry and timings.
You should forget
about the competition.
Keep it in the back of
your mind and not the forefront.
Relax, enjoy.
What's the worst that can happen?
You'll come in second or third?
You are anyway coming second or third.
So, why not...
Give a free rein,
and then watch
how your horse races ahead.
Mare. Whatever.
Got it?
I'm going back to practise now.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Swim like a fish, Kartika.
Swim like a...
Faster, Kartika.
You will have to swim, you know.
No one's going to push you forward.
Faster, Kartika.
Kartika,
giving your 100% isn't enough.
You need to give 101% to win.
Faster! Come on!
We don't have time to waste.
Even I can do better than this.
What are you doing, Kartika?
What?
Stop doing that. I am coming out.
You're blind?
Can't you see that
I'm doing my bloody best?
Got it.
What?
Sit.
Come on, sit down.
You cannot win like this, Kartika.
What do you mean?
I am your friend.
I have a plan.
I'll help you win. Trust me.
I'll break the legs
of that Manipur girl.
I'll add laxative
to that Bengal girl's breakfast.
I'll have the Kerala girl kidnapped.
You don't have to worry
about a thing.
You call this your "bloody best"?
This is your "bloody best"? This!
You think I am doing this
for myself?
Kartika...
you need to decide whether
you want to be Nemo,
or the shark from Jaws?
Mr. Jaws of Jalandhar,
why don't you show me
how it's done?
Stop seducing me.
Crazy woman!
I don't know how to swim.
Are you crazy?
I can't swim.
-I am telling the truth.
-I think he's drowning, dude.
Come on, Kartika.
What are you doing?
-I can't swim.
-Jaggi, stop overacting.
Crazy woman!
He seems like a method actor.
He can change his profession.
Shit!
Oh, shit!
-Go call Damle sir.
-Yeah.
Just call the medic.
Jaggi?
Jaggi, okay?
You okay?
I'm... I'm so sorry. I...
You fine?
I... I literally had no idea.
I'm... I'm so sorry.
You kissed me.
What?
I just gave you CPR.
You can call it whatever you want,
but, where I am from,
we call that a kiss.
And from where I am, people
like you are called fucking idiots.
I'll tell everyone
that you kissed me.
I am doomed.
Just a sec.
Wait for a second.
Sorry.
Not cool, okay?
Fine. Sorry.
Let's go.
I'm not going anywhere.
"No distance, no boundaries"
"There are no limits
When it comes to love"
"It is so overwhelming"
"The obsession never fades away"
"I cannot take it anymore
I want to touch your soul"
"I cannot wait
At the shore anymore"
"I am obsessed with you"
"This world is nothing without you"
"You ruin me"
"You complete me"
"Nothing's right or wrong anymore"
"Now that you are my soulmate"
"You ruin me"
"You complete me"
"Nothing's right or wrong anymore"
"Now that you are my soulmate"
1 minute 3 seconds.
This is your best timing so far.
Kartika, this timing can
take you to the finals.
"Intoxicating
Yes, intoxicating"
"Your eyes are intoxicating"
"I'll drown in them
I'll surely drown in them"
"I'll never be able
To resurface again"
"I have got hooked
To a strange obsession this time"
"I keep chanting your name
Day and night"
"I am obsessed with you"
-"This world is nothing without you"
-Come on, faster.
You are not Nemo! You are a shark!
"You ruin me"
"You complete me"
"Nothing's right or wrong anymore"
"Now that you are my soulmate"
"You ruin me"
"You complete me"
"Nothing's right or wrong anymore"
"Now that you are my soulmate"
"You ruin me"
"You complete me"
"Nothing's right..."
Here's your room.
Bye.
Now that's what you call a kiss.
Your flight just landed, Uncle?
She's not answering your call?
Oh, yeah, yeah, Uncle.
She was practising all night.
Yeah. Hard-core practice.
Lap after lap after lap after lap...
Very dedicated, Uncle.
She trains till late.
Shit.
Uncle...
No, she's in the washroom.
I'll have her call you back?
Sure, Uncle.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Come on, come on,
come on, Kartika. Come on.
Come on, Kartika! Come on.
Go for it, mermaid!
Go, go, go.
Yes, yes, yes. Come on!
Go, go, go! Hold this.
Come on, come on, Kartika. Come on.
Who is he?
Go, Kartika!
Come on!
-Come on!
-Yes!
Go for it.
Come on, Kartika!
-Come on.
-Come on, Kartika!
Yes.
Come on, Kartika!
-Oh, my God!
-Come on, Kartika!
Come on, Kartika!
Go for it.
Go, go, go!
Come on!
Yes, yes, yes!
She won! She won! She won!
Kartika!
There she is, our winner.
-Congratulations. Finally!
-You did great.
-I'm so proud of you, kiddo.
-Congratulations.
Thanks, Dad.
That was awesome, champion.
You swam like a fish.
I told you losing
the weight would do it.
Your friend?
Yes, Mom, of course.
Jagg... Joginder.
Just helped me out with my training,
that's it.
I see.
Hello, Joginder.
Hello.
What do you do?
I play centre forward
for Punjab Honkey Team.
-Centre forward, okay. That's great.
-Mom, let's leave?
Don't forget to invite him.
For your birthday?
Why didn't you tell me? When is it?
No, for her wedding.
It takes place in 3 months.
In London.
Are you okay?
-Are you fine?
-He's good, Dad.
-He's fine.
-I'm sorry.
Yes, sorry.
-He's fine.
-Sorry.
Listen, Kartika, just look
at these cards and pick one.
This is not the place.
-I don't want any last-minute hassles.
-Not now, Mom.
Look at this. So sweet, isn't it?
Pretty it is.
It has not been finalised as yet.
What? The wedding?
No, the wedding has been finalised,
but not the card.
-Shall we?
-I'll make you meet Damle sir?
-Let's go.
-Oh, okay.
Let's go meet Damle.
Poor thing.
Zip it, guys.
If you go to see, she practically
used him for his body.
And then gave him a wedding invite.
Stop it. It's not so.
Good thing too.
Now I won't have to bear
her responsibility anymore.
She's now
that London guy's responsibility.
I have to go and become a star.
I have to become rich.
You just wait and watch
how I'll score goals now.
On every goal, every girl
in the stadium will stand and go,
"Jaggi, I love you."
"Hey, Jaggi, I love you."
Bro! This isn't cricket.
We are hockey players.
At the most,
you'll get a decent job
in the army or the railways, thanks
to the sports quota. Right, Jaggi?
By the way,
that guy in London doesn't know
that Jaggi has already had
his share of fun with her.
True.
She is so smart.
-You are one lucky bastard, Jaggi.
-I agree.
If I knew this,
I too have tried my luck.
-You fucking...
-Hey!
Kartika!
Karti...
What?
Come down, please.
Cut it. Now.
What?
Why didn't you tell me
that you're getting married?
Why should I tell you?
Are you crazy?
Why are you being so rude?
I deleted Tinder because of you.
I hit Rane with a hockey stick.
The poor guy is in so much pain.
Hang on a sec. I never told you
to do those things.
Just download the app again.
Apologise to Rane.
Why are you blaming me?
Jaggi, I don't want
to make it complicated.
Fine. Let bygone be bygones.
I am sorry.
Can we move on?
What "sorry"?
Is this a board game?
I'll apologise to him,
you'll apologise to me.
Kartika, don't you think
what you did was--
What I did? What do you mean?
Hang on. What?
No, it is not so.
What I did?
What are you referring to?
If you are trying to guilt-trip me
for what happened last night,
then let me just tell you
I'm not that kind of a girl.
If this is what this conversation
is about, then I am not interested.
-I don't want to have this conversation.
-Wait, Kartika.
Stop or else...
Or else, what?
I'll delete your number.
Go for it, dude.
-I'm deleting it.
-Very mature. Do it.
Happy?
Try calling me now.
I've blocked you.
Jaggi, I am sorry.
Fine, I should have told you,
I know.
But I didn't plan this.
What happened between us
just happened.
I have other plans.
I'm moving back to London.
I'm getting married there, so...
Good, no?
But all the very best.
I'm sure you're gonna
do well in life and...
We can stay in touch and...
This isn't a bouquet.
This one's from my heart.
Got it?
Tell Sheena I'm going to
chop off her ponytail one day.
"Whenever I see a beautiful girl
My crazy heart goes ole-ole..."
"Let's sing to the rhythm
And dance..."
I really hope he doesn't show up.
I can't deal with him right now.
Don't say that.
I'm here for the drama.
Thanks.
Anytime.
Guys, give it up for wrestler
Bhawani Singh from Rohtak.
Do we have any other multitalented
person in the audience
who can come up on
this stage and perform?
Anyone? Anybody?
Hey!
No, he won't.
What are you doing, Jaggi?
Why not?
-Jaggi, please.
-I am going.
No, he won't. Don't cause a scene.
He'll surely sing
a serious sad song.
I can't... I can't deal with him.
"Yamma, yamma
Yamma, yamma"
"Such a beautiful atmosphere"
"Yamma, yamma
Yamma, yamma"
"Such a beautiful atmosphere"
"Tonight is all we have"
"Tomorrow who knows
Where we will be"
"Tonight is all we have"
"Tomorrow who knows
Where we will be"
"Yamma, yamma
Yamma, yamma"
"Such a beautiful atmosphere"
"Tonight is all we have"
"Tomorrow who knows
Where we will be"
"Tonight is all we have"
"Tomorrow who knows
Where we will be"
You are something!
I just can't figure you out.
I honestly thought
you'll break into a sad song.
I am not that kind of a boy.
Crying is such a waste
of time and energy.
This is the best part
about being a Punjabi.
No matter if we feel like
"Humpty Dumpty had a great fall,"
we'll always sing a cheerful song.
Okay.
-Listen?
-What?
Don't marry him, please.
Jaggi, don't bore me, please.
The wedding was fixed
before I came here.
I hadn't planned that I'd meet you.
Life happens.
We can be friends.
Why don't you be friends
with your fiance instead?
I love you.
You don't love me.
You are just in shock after
you heard the news of my wedding.
-Hey--
-I'll explain it to you logically.
See, you came to the pool,
you clicked my pictures.
That wasn't love, right?
Then you attended my practice
sessions. I'll say similar zone.
-So, not love.
-Okay.
Then you helped me.
That was sweet. Thank you.
But I believe that was
a fellow sportsman thing to do.
It wasn't love.
So, I rest my case right here.
And what about what happened
between us that night?
You can call it anything you want.
Hook up or sex, take your pick.
Definitely not love. Yeah.
I'm damn sure.
Can't fool me.
-You are so confident.
-I know.
You know nothing about yourself,
but you claim to know me.
Kartika, you should give us
a chance.
Forget about the wedding.
What is this nonsense?
Aren't you underage?
No, I am not underage.
And one doesn't only
get married for love.
What else does one get married for?
-To settle down.
-Huh?
See, everything will be quite rosy
in the beginning,
because initial days of course.
Then after a while,
say, after 10 years,
my waist will be wider by 10 inches
because I would've had kids.
So yeah, figure will go for a toss.
I don't have a problem with that.
I am okay with it.
Hear me out.
I'll look boring.
I'll get a tad irritating because
I'll be raising the kids on my own.
My husband will not
be helping me with it.
I'll vent out my anger on him.
I'll become an emotional eater.
My waist will keep expanding
and compete with an IMAX screen.
After some time,
I'll start facing midlife crisis.
-If nothing works, there's therapy.
-Right.
Chocolate therapy is there,
retail therapy is there.
"Therapy" therapy is there, so...
You should try laughter therapy
as well.
Not funny.
Girl, is this a marriage
or a suicide mission?
This is what happens
in a marriage, Jaggi.
I know. I have witnessed it. Yeah.
Oh, really?
But the good thing is
we won't have to go through this.
We won't get to the point
where we know each other so well
that we'll get bored of each other.
So, good.
This is how our story shall be,
short and sweet.
Yeah.
Kartika, if this is what you think,
you are yet to witness true love.
You have based your philosophy
on cheap fake goods.
Listen...
I love you...
till the end
and not just till the interval.
I come with a lifetime guarantee.
Look into my eyes and
say that you love him.
What is this? Just...
Just say it, and I'll leave.
What does it mean?
I... I don't...
Why...
You failed.
Look, I don't care about your exes,
affairs or fiances...
because I'm the love of your life,
your number one.
I love you.
Just cancel the wedding.
Cancel the wedding, please.
What?
Cancel the wedding.
How difficult can it be?
Have you gone crazy?
It is not that easy.
I mean... no.
Just tell your mom, "I don't love him.
I love Jaggi," and cancel the wedding.
-I am not impractical.
-She has already met me.
How is that possible?
So what if she has met you?
-What?
-So what?
-I love you.
-Fine. Okay, fine.
If you continue to feel
the same way even after 3 months,
come to London,
I'll cancel my wedding.
-You promise?
-I promise.
What's that movie with
Shah Rukh Khan in it?
DDLJ!
DDLJ-style, I'll cancel my wedding.
I promise.
-You won't back out?
-I won't.
Okay, now can we
please enjoy ourselves?
You were just singing
"Yamma, yamma..."
"Tonight is all we have"
"Tomorrow who knows
Where we will be"
Can we do that?
Perfect.
"O gracious one"
"From the time
I laid my eyes on you"
"O gracious one"
"I cannot take my eyes off you"
"I want to trap you in my eyes"
"I want you to be mine"
"My love"
"O God
Can I call her my soulmate?"
"My confidant"
"O God
Can I call her my soulmate?"
"My confidant"
"When I look into her eyes"
"When she speaks to me"
"I hear melody"
"O God
Can I call her my soulmate?"
"My confidant"
"All I wanted was a drop
And I was offered the ocean"
"The sun appeared
And the darkness disappeared"
"I swear I am all yours"
"I swear
I have lost my heart to you"
"This isn't just a passing phase"
"I want to trap you in my eyes"
"I want you to be mine"
"My love"
"O God
Can I call her my soulmate?"
"My confidant"
"O God
Can I call her my soulmate?"
"My confidant"
Kartika!
So, you came here with
a wedding card instead of a visa?
A wedding card that has
someone else's name printed on it.
I had no other option, bro.
I had applied for a visa.
My application got rejected.
The agent ran away
with all my money.
I had no option left.
We were just a palm's
distance away from each other.
You know, my friends thought
I'd lost my mind.
I haven't told my mom anything.
I left a letter under
her pillow and came here.
It says, "I'll be back soon."
I know I'll get thrashed
when I go back.
It's okay.
I know you'll understand.
Your speech is what
inspired me so much.
"If we hadn't met in Paris,
we would've met in Amsterdam.
"If not Amritsar, then Chandigarh.
"I'd find you in any corner of
the world because you are my destiny.
"I love you."
Listen... that was a different time,
a different place.
It was a simple wedding
reception speech. That's it.
No, bro, don't say that.
It wasn't just a speech.
It was a philosophy...
a philosophy on love.
It touched
the deepest part of my heart.
So, you came here because
of my philosophy, right?
Then here's my new philosophy.
After you hear that,
you'll insist on going back to India.
What's the big deal?
I said I'm sorry.
Not for speaking the truth.
I still feel that
what I said was right.
But this wasn't the right place
or time for it, and so I am sorry.
You are sorry?
Wow!
He's the Central Minister, Ira.
It was an official
diplomatic dinner.
It wasn't a street rally protest.
I invited you to have dinner with
my superiors, not to fight with them.
If someone has political views
that are different from ours,
we start respecting that
and not start attacking it.
But you being you...
You were there as my wife.
You were not there as
some two-bit social activist.
Excuse me? How dare you!
My position never mattered to you.
You don't care.
-Gautam, listen to me.
-No, you listen to me.
This isn't the first time.
And I am sure this won't
be the last time either.
Sir, keychain?
Ma'am, keychain?
Just five euros, ma'am.
Please.
You are from Pakistan?
India?
Same here. Please take one.
Have you eaten?
No, not since two days.
Wait here. I'll be right back.
What's your name?
Aditya.
Where are you from?
Saharanpur.
Where do you stay?
Here and there.
There's a camp across
the 18th Street metro.
I usually stay there.
30-40 of us live there.
Indians, Pakistanis,
Bangladeshis and Africans.
French police had received a tip-off
about an illegal settlement.
Many young men and children
have been arrested.
Move!
These illegal immigrants,
most of who are Indians,
will soon be deported.
He's the same boy who...
This is Rajesh Kambode with
cameraman Rakesh Yadav reporting live...
Did you tip off the police?
Look at me, Gautam!
Did you tell the police
about that settlement?
Calm down, Ira.
Calm down?
Yes, I did. So?
Will you allow a stranger
to stay in your house?
You won't, right?
Then why should France allow it?
They are all illegals.
You are taking revenge, aren't you?
Because I argued
with that minister?
You have lost your mind, Ira.
I am talking to you.
I am listening.
Who are you, Gautam?
You are not the man I married.
I am the same man.
I am the same "plan man" Gautam.
I thought you'd change
after we get married.
You'd become a bit more mature.
Look, Ira, I'm a government servant.
I am just an employee.
Unlike you, I cannot just start
protesting at the drop of a hat.
Why do you keep insulting me
with reference to my job?
I am not insulting.
I have no problem
with your job either.
You are the one who
has a problem with my job.
I have a problem with you!
I married you Gautam,
not the Government of India.
Okay, look.
Look... Ira!
-Please, let's not fight.
-No, Gautam. Please.
Come on, first get out of your
"Bhagat Singh" revolutionary zone.
Please?
I love you, Ira.
I really do, right?
I love you too, Gautam.
But I don't like you.
I just don't like you anymore.
I...
I feel suffocated here.
I need some space.
I don't know what to do.
I... I need to leave.
I want to go.
I need to go, please.
Please let me go.
I'll call you a taxi.
Heard enough?
This was part two
of my love story.
Short and sweet.
Now get inspired by it,
and tell me that
you want to go back to India.
Not now, bro.
Please don't do that.
I have come so far for her.
How can I just go back?
Please help me move forward, bro.
You don't get it, huh?
You have nothing
to move forward to.
You came here for nothing.
That girl is willingly getting
married to someone else, you fool.
No one is waiting for you.
Your love story
does not have a happy ending.
It will only lead you to your doom.
Don't you get that?
Kismet, fate,
destiny, it's all rubbish.
Marfatia, complete this
boy's paperwork urgently.
And book him
the next flight to India.
Please don't, bro.
I'll personally escort him
to the airport.
Hello?
Sir, you'll have to wait at
the airport hotel for some time.
I'll call you once
I am done with the paperwork.
Things are delayed as of now.
Yeah, Marfatia. I am at
the airport hotel, room 405.
What's the delay?
Sir, two more illegals
are being deported.
It is taking some time
to process their paperwork.
I need 20 minutes more, sir.
Okay. Make that quick, please.
And call me as soon as
you are here. I'll head down.
Yeah.
-Jaggi!
-Sorry, bro!
Jaggi!
Jaggi, stop!
What are you doing?
Down... get down.
Don't be mad, Jaggi.
What are you doing?
Listen to me. Get down.
Don't be a fool.
You gave up too soon, bro.
I won't give up.
I have to go and meet Kartika.
-Jaggi, don't do it.
-I have to go and meet Kartika.
-You don't get it.
-No, Jaggi. Listen to me.
-I'll jump, bro. Step away.
-Don't be stupid. Give me your hand.
-No, bro.
-It's quite a fall, Jaggi.
-I'll jump.
-Shut up, Jaggi.
-Don't be stupid. Give me your hand.
-You should step away. I'll jump.
-Jaggi, listen to me.
You should step away,
I am going to jump.
-Give me your hand, Jaggi.
-Bro!
Jaggi!
-Jaggi, you... Stop moving!
-Please let go of my hand, bro.
Please let go, bro.
Let me go.
Stop moving
or else we both will die.
Grab my hand and come up.
Grab my hand, come on.
Come up, Jaggi.
Give me your hand, come on.
Come up, yeah, yeah.
Yes.
Yeah, come on.
Yeah, yeah. Come on.
Yeah.
Bloody fool.
Sorry, bro.
See you later.
Airport, train station,
bus station...
I have sent his picture
everywhere, sir.
But I think he will go
into hiding for a few days.
No chance, Marfatia.
He'll make another attempt.
He's in a hurry.
He knows Eurotunnel has
tight security and he'll get caught.
[speaking French]
There's only one way to get from France
to London, and that is Calais.
The same place where
he was caught the last time.
He'll make another attempt
from there, Marfatia.
I'm heading to Calais.
Jaggi! Jaggi!
They released you?
Bilal.
How are you?
What happened?
It's nothing.
Bilal, I need to reach London
by Monday morning at any cost.
There has to be a way.
It is possible if you have cash.
It is impossible otherwise.
Do you have cash?
I just have a return ticket
to India.
The one that they gave me
while deporting me. Will that do?
Forget that. What were you saying
about your cousin?
He told me...
[speaking Pashto]
Throw him out.
-Where's the money?
-Come on.
-Get up.
-What are you doing?
Why are you hitting me?
What are you doing?
-Check his pockets.
-What are you doing? I...
Shut up!
-Check his pockets.
-I don't have any money.
-Shut up!
-Check his pockets.
No, I don't have any money.
From where do I get the money?
I don't have any money.
-Don't move.
-Where are you hiding it?
Give it to me.
Why are you hitting him?
Hey... I have the money.
Come here.
I have the money.
I'll give it to you.
-Come here, Lala.
-I have the money.
I'll give it you.
I just need to make a phone call.
-I'll get the money.
-Whom will you call?
There is a guy who works
for the Indian Embassy.
He got me out of
the detention centre.
I'll call him and
ask him to get the money.
Buzz off, kiddo.
Bro, phone.
Here.
-Hurry up.
-I'm trying to recall his number.
He doesn't even remember his number.
So, basically, at a sangeet party,
everybody has to perform.
So... Just one second.
Hello?
Kartika?
It's me, Jaggi.
Hi!
Shit. Okay.
Of course, Jaggi, of...
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
Hi, sorry, how are you? Sorry.
I am good.
Listen, I am in France.
I'll be in London soon.
Hang on a second,
what do you mean by France?
What else can France mean?
France, Calais, DDLJ.
I'll soon be in London.
Get ready to cancel the wedding.
Hurry up, ask for 5,000 bucks.
I will ask. Hold on.
Let me at least say hi.
-Ask him to hurry up.
-Hello?
Shit, you almost scared me,
you idiot.
You fool, if I hadn't heard
Pinky and Rane in the background,
I would have believed you.
Anyway, how's Amritsar?
How's everything?
I am not in Amritsar, love.
Pinky and Rane are not with me.
You should go and inform
your parents that I am coming.
Jaggi, please stop kidding.
It's not funny.
It's not something to joke about,
so please...
They will get
the shock of their lives.
What are you doing?
Don't joke... Hello?
He's talking to a girl.
I am not talking to a girl.
He has a thin voice.
What's going on, Jaggi?
Listen, I...
-He is lying.
-I am not talking to a girl.
What's the commotion about?
-Listen, I am coming. I have...
-Jaggi?
-Hello?
-Let go of the phone.
Let go of the phone. Let it go.
Let go of the phone.
-Jaggi?
-I have..
Hello? Hello?
Hello, sorry,
the phone slipped off my hands.
Keep talking, Kartika.
Jaggi, will you stop kidding me?
What's going on? Hello?
-Kartika...
-Give me the phone.
It's been so long
since I heard your voice.
-[speaking French]
-I love your voice.
-Hang on a second, what's going on?
-Don't worry.
I am coming, okay?
You should...
Listen... Kartika, I love you.
What the...
What?
[in French] The number you are trying
to reach is currently unavailable.
Please try again later.
It's French, the number.
He's in bloody France, babe.
Will you keep it lower?
We all know he's crazy.
Must be joking, I don't know.
I didn't ask him to come.
Excuse me, ma'am,
I'm from the Indian Embassy.
I'm looking for an Indian guy
called Jaggi.
Are you...
Was this a joke?
We both could have been dead!
Fool!
Sorry, bro.
Sorry.
I'm bringing him back to Paris.
What's the status of the flight?
It has already departed, sir.
No jump seats are available
for tonight, in any flight.
We can try tomorrow.
Inform the detention centre.
I'll drop him there.
What's that, bro?
The sea.
And what's across the sea?
Dover, England.
For real?
Can you please stop
the car for a second?
Please. Just let me take
a look at it. Please, bro.
I am begging you.
Just for a minute.
Shut up.
Please, bro.
Just let me take a look at it.
There, I stopped the car. Happy?
Can I get down to
take a better look at it?
You wish.
I cannot go anywhere
in this state.
And you are going to
deport me anyway.
Please let me get down
and take a better look at it.
Thank you, thank you very much.
Dover means England,
which means London.
It's just
a thumb's distance away now.
It seems quite close, bro.
-20 miles.
-That's it? Just 20 miles?
One can easily swim the distance.
Go.
Go and swim to your destination.
One less headache for me.
Get in there and we won't
even be able to recover your body.
I won't even have to take
the trouble of deporting you.
-Really?
-Really.
Heavy currents,
sub-zero temperature.
You'll freeze to death
in ten minutes.
If I am lucky and you end up
under a ferry's propeller,
then you'll be mincemeat.
Come on, don't be so pessimistic.
You used to be so romantic.
You have become so aggressive now.
Really, you want me
under a propeller?
I could do with some good news,
Marfatia.
Sir, the detention centre
is closed.
What do you mean closed?
It's not a resort that they
can close. Get them to open it.
Sir, they won't take
him back without court orders.
Also, it's a weekend, sir.
This is not India.
Everyone's gone home.
Oh, by the way,
I spoke to Murli at the airport.
His flight leaves
on Monday morning.
What do you mean by his flight
leaves on Monday morning?
What do I do with him
for the next two days?
There is no other option, sir.
What do we do now?
Dance over my head.
-Don't laugh.
-I didn't laugh, sir.
Not you, Marfatia.
I'll get back.
Okay.
When you want something
with all your heart and mind,
all the universe conspires
in helping you to achieve it.
Look, I will have to
tolerate you for two days.
You have a couple of options.
Your first option is... this.
No, bro, what are you saying?
-I'll do as you say.
-Good.
By God!
When the nurse said, "Eat something
before you take a pill,"
she meant a buttered toast,
an apple or something like that.
She didn't mean you gobble down
everything in the restaurant.
You know, my mother always says,
"It's a sin to interrupt anyone
when they are eating."
You are a Tinder generation Romeo.
You don't know shit about love.
You love philosophies, don't you?
Here's another one.
Life is like a buffet.
First comes the salad counter,
followed by the pickles counter,
then comes the main course,
a variety of dishes,
followed by dessert in the end.
Your problem is that
you have stopped at the salad bar,
and you assume that
this is all that is being offered.
You are wrong.
Keep going ahead.
Check out the variety.
You'll go crazy.
Are you getting me?
Go say hi to her
and introduce yourself.
Go on.
Really?
But I am quite weak in French.
Refrain from speaking in Punjabi,
and she'll teach you French.
Here.
Go, offer her a drink.
Thank you.
Listen?
Don't try to run away.
I am sitting right here.
Can I sit?
Yes.
You lot love to say yes.
Hi, hi.
My name is Jaggi.
What is your name?
[in French] My name is Emily.
Emily. Okay.
Rue num...
"Number 3, Rue De La Rouge."
-"Rue" means road.
-Okay.
Can we go there?
You are fast.
Wait a second.
That girl gave you her address,
and you want me to take you there?
I am not your chauffeur.
I am a high commission officer
who is about to deport you. Got it?
-Let's go.
-I never said you are my chauffer.
You are my brother.
You are my guru.
I am not that kind of a boy.
You misunderstand.
I come from a decent family.
I know you quite well.
Let's go.
This will at least stop you
from going gaga over that girl.
We've reached your destination.
Rue number three.
We are here.
Pull over, bro.
Stop, stop, stop.
[speaking French]
Si.
-La.
-[speaking French]
[speaking French]
I don't want a tie, uncle.
Size.
Then say that.
Stop talking nonsense, yeah.
Just hold one second?
Can I have your phone, bro?
I'll ask Kartika what her size is.
Thank you.
Shortlist this one. It's good.
You talk to him.
I don't care.
-Hel... Whoa!
-Hello?
-Hello, Kartika?
-What's your dress size?
Huh?
We know you are using a computer
to call from a French number,
so the joke is done, Jaggi.
Why would I joke, darling?
You don't believe me?
You want proof? Wait,
I'll send you a picture. Hang on.
What?
You want me to believe
that you came all the way from
Amritsar to France in a plane?
Who said anything about a plane?
I came here hitchhiking.
It's not funny, Jaggi.
Have you gone crazy?
What are you saying?
Yes, I am crazy about it.
Now quickly tell me your dress size.
I am in a shop. I have company.
Okay fine, that's it.
Okay, you're stretching it too far.
Stop joking.
I wasn't joking back then.
And I am not joking now.
I am here for you.
Try to understand, Kartika.
I love you.
I am getting married, Jaggi.
Why are you saying this?
We will get married.
We will get married to each other.
But we will have a torrid affair
before that.
A crazy love affair.
You said if I come, you'll cancel
your wedding. So here I am.
Okay, okay, stop it, okay.
I was just joking.
Are you crazy?
I wouldn't say
such things seriously.
What?
What are you expecting?
That you'll come here
and I'll cancel my wedding?
That is not gonna happen, okay?
Fine, I like you.
-I know.
-See, that's what I am talking about.
You are crazy.
You don't listen to me.
You are impractical.
Jaggi, please...
Hello?
Okay, my battery is low.
Listen to me carefully.
If you are really in France,
please go back.
Listen, Kartika...
you are my number one,
and I am your number one.
Do you get that?
Hello?
She got so busy scolding me that
she forgot to tell me her dress size.
Her phone's battery is dead.
I know.
And she stays in a remote village of
London where there is no electricity.
-Hello?
-Yeah?
Size?
Hips?
Chest?
Bro, ask him to behave
or I end up slapping him.
Tell him her size.
Size?
One second.
Height is...
Wrong model.
Okay.
Watch me.
So when we hug, it's...
This much.
Height....
Shoulder, height, waist.
[speaking French]
Voila?
-Perfect.
-Discount 50%.
Really?
Thanks, uncle.
"My beloved is my wealth"
"My beloved is my downfall"
"The love we share
Bears witness to that"
"My beloved is my wealth"
"My beloved is my downfall"
"The love we share
Bears witness to that"
"My love"
"I pray for your long life"
"I want the memories of your love"
"To forever stay engraved
In my heart"
How about some privacy, bro?
There's cereal, milk.
Here you go.
Coffee.
Bro?
You miss her?
I mean the food.
All the delicious Indian delicacies
that she cooked.
Now you only eat
cereals and mueslis.
You miss it, don't you?
I can feel it.
It is visible in your eyes.
Forget your feeling
and just finish this.
I see!
You had an affair.
Oh, shut up.
This is life.
Life.
Stop acting
like a forlorn lover, bro.
Fine, so she got upset and left.
Why can't you go and
convince her to come back?
Go and get her.
Okay, I too will come with you.
Stop getting so excited
and sit down.
Ira wanted to leave.
This is what she wanted.
-End of story.
-How can it end here?
Tell me, what did you do
to convince her?
Did you apologise?
Did you cry? Did you beg?
Did you grovel at her feet
or bow before her?
You didn't.
Look at me.
You are a stalker.
Me a stalker?
Yes.
What...
What are you doing?
I'm calling Ira.
Give me my phone.
Give me my phone back!
-Gautam?
-Give me my...
Hello?
Hello, Gautam?
Hi.
Did you call me by mistake?
No.
I mean, I was just...
Strange that you called.
I was just about to call you.
-Okay.
-Can we meet today?
Lunch?
It's okay if you are busy.
I understand.
No... I mean, yes, I can.
Sure.
-Near your office?
-Yeah.
One o'clock?
Sounds perfect.
I'll see you soon.
See you.
You should smile more often, bro.
Your face lights up.
You look so nice.
Hi.
Ira!
How are you?
Who are you?
It's me, Jaggi.
Remember,
I had attended your wedding?
"Whose side are you from?"
"Me? I am from my side."
Oh, yeah, I remember.
What brings you here, Jaggi?
Actually, I am getting married.
-Oh, congratulations.
-Thank you.
So, I came to invite you
and Gautam.
Thanks.
Jaggi, why don't you
order something for yourself?
Sure. Okay.
Okay.
Bye.
What is he doing with you?
Long story, Ira.
Actually, I have to deport him.
Deport?
Then why is he so happy?
He suffers from
perpetual happiness.
Good for him.
You and I,
we are quite different, Gautam.
I guess we never really
had a chance, did we?
You... you're happy with
just the shades of blue.
I see red, green, violet,
blacks... but you only see blue.
You only see blue.
We're so different.
Anyway, there's a civil lawyer
in my office.
He has prepared our divorce papers.
You just need to sign them.
You can first read them, of course.
And this belongs to you.
I was wondering,
if I had this thermal swimsuit,
I could swim to London.
After all, it's just 20 miles away.
No, it's okay.
Maybe some other time.
No worries.
Show me how you'll swim.
Come on, it's just 20 miles.
You can do it, come on.
No, no, no, no, no.
You won't have anything
to take support from out there.
You are Superman.
Love is your superpower, right?
So go and swim.
Go. Swim.
Come on, swim!
Made it to London already?
You cannot swim across
the English Channel.
You should have that
engraved in your brain.
That girl is not waiting for you.
You won't be getting married to her.
Your love story is over.
It's over!
Your flight for India
leaves on Monday,
and that's when
this door will open.
Gautam?
Gautam!
Gautam! Wake up!
Are you okay?
What's going on?
What are you doing here?
You called me at four
in the morning.
When I woke up, I saw
I had 10 missed calls from you.
I've been trying to call you back
the whole morning.
I didn't call you, okay?
I called you?
Yes.
Gautam, note.
"Whether I reach my destination
or not lies in the hands of God."
But I will die if I don't even try.
That's why I am going.
I have taken some cash
from your wallet.
Sorry for the trouble.
And thank you...
for taking such good care of me.
We both have to cross
some borders, bro.
We both have a long way
ahead of us.
I am trying with all my heart
and soul to reach Kartika.
Bro, you haven't tried until you try
with all your heart and soul.
May God be with you.
What is this, Gautam?
That boy...
what did he do?
You have a voicemail.
Kartika, I am coming.
Please wait for me
if I get held up.
If there is a God you believe in,
please pray for me, will you?
I love you.
Hello, Jaggi?
This is Gautam.
Sir, this is Kartika.
Is he there?
Sir, I got a voicemail.
He was saying something
about swimming.
Can I just talk to him, sir?
I... I just want to
talk to him right now.
We're still figuring it out.
Figuring it out? As in what?
He's missing.
I'll call you back as soon
as I find out anything, okay?
Who was that?
He is madly in love with this girl.
He wants to swim across
the English Channel
and go to London to meet her.
Can you believe this?
He's crazy. He will die.
He's an idiot.
I need to do something.
It's a suicide.
I'll have to do something.
Look, I'm really sorry he shouldn't
have involved you in this.
He shouldn't have disturbed you.
I'm really sorry.
No, Gautam.
You don't have to be sorry.
This is much bigger
than you and me.
He could die.
Look, you should contact
the coast guard.
I've got volunteers along the coast
who can help us find Jaggi.
So, just let me help you, okay?
"I want make you my god
So that I can worship you"
"I pray for your companionship
So that I seek support from you"
"I want to pray and ask for you"
"I want you engraved in my heart"
"I want you to be a habit
I can never let go of"
"I want to make you my passion"
"I want to make you my fate"
"I want you to be my love"
"I want you to be
My heartfelt prayer"
"I want you to be a habit
I can never let go of"
"I want to make you my passion"
"I want to make you my fate"
"I want you to be my love"
"I want you to be
My heartfelt prayer"
"I want you to be a habit
I can never let go of"
"I want to make you my passion"
"Why are we bound by limitations?"
"Why are we restricted
By boundaries?"
"Why do we have so much distance
Between us?"
"When our destination is the same"
"Why are our paths not the same?"
"I want to set an example for love"
"I want to pen our love story
On water"
Jaggi, you are not Nemo.
You are a shark.
-Come on, come on, come on...
-"Be that resounding inkling"
"I want to make you my passion"
"I want you to dwell in my heart"
"I want to stay wordless
And make you my smile"
"I want you to be
A blessing from God"
"I want to make you my passion"
"I want to make you my fate"
"I want you to be my love"
"I want you to be
My heartfelt prayer"
"I want you to be a habit
I can never let go of"
"I want to make you my passion"
"This sea shall bear my witness"
"You can call it a sin
Or call it love"
"I want you to be
My judge and jury"
"I want to make you my passion"
He was trying to cross the
English Channel to be with you.
The coast guard saved him
from drowning.
Is he mad?
Is he out of his mind?
What?
Is he fine, sir?
Yes, he is fine.
I'm so... I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Can I ask you something?
Yes?
Would you have cancelled your wedding
had he made it to London?
No.
I don't know.
I... I don't know. I...
I was clear, sir.
I was quite clear about it.
Of course, it...
I mean I am practical.
I have a brain. Of course,
I wouldn't cancel my wedding.
I don't know.
Are you feeling guilty?
It's not guilt, sir. I...
I might not be able
to explain it. I...
Who does such a thing, sir?
In this day and age...
How does one deal
with so much love, sir?
I am confused, sir.
What should I do?
You need to decide, Kartika.
You need to think
before you decide.
Don't make an emotional decision.
The decision is easy
if you love him.
And it is even easier
if you don't love him.
You remember when you were nine,
your mom and I used to argue a lot?
Do you remember that?
There was someone else in my life.
I was very happy with her.
Your mom and I,
we are friends, but...
you know.
I contemplated leaving you for her.
But I didn't.
I chose you.
I chose my family.
Over myself, my feelings and love.
And you know what?
I made the right decision.
You take after me, Kartika.
You are a realist.
You are practical.
You are not a romantic fool.
Forget what happened
at the sports camp.
Think about your future.
You have a long way ahead of you.
You have to make
a life for yourself...
with Karan.
Do you understand?
Bro, you know...
Sohni used to swim across River Chenab
every day to meet Mahiwal.
And I couldn't...
I couldn't do it even once.
-Hello?
-What the hell were you thinking?
What exactly was going
on in your mind?
What if something would
have happened to you?
You keep telling me that you love me.
That's how much you love me?
You know what I was
going through over here?
-I...
-I what? Stop stammering.
This isn't a joke.
I am getting married.
And look at what
you are doing to me.
Jaggi, you are immature, impractical,
and a fucking Avengers-level idiot!
And I am even worse...
because I love you.
Huh? What?
I love you.
You idiot.
I love you too, Kartika.
Now stop smiling.
You are dancing with joy,
aren't you?
No.
A little?
Tell me.
No.
I love you.
Do you plan to marry her
over the phone,
or do you want to go there?
Let's go.
We have a lot of work to do.
Good morning, Marfatia.
Really sorry to disturb you
on a Sunday.
Just tell me something
in which cabinet do we keep
the files of damaged,
stolen and missing passports?
6D, sir.
-Some problem, sir?
-No, no.
I can come to the office.
It will just take me half an hour.
No, no, no.
No, Marfatia.
If there's anything else,
I'll call you.
So, you want me to
cancel the wedding?
It is my wedding, Dad.
I'll decide.
Didn't you hear anything
I said back then?
I heard you, Dad.
Dad, I choose myself.
Not you, not Mom,
and definitely not Karan.
How can I keep anyone happy
if I am not happy?
You think you had
made the right decision?
You say you did it for your family.
Do we have a family?
Are you happy?
Can you see what I have become?
Dad, if you had left me and Mom
for a couple of years
or left us forever for that matter,
it would have been problematic
for some time,
but we would have managed it.
Trust me, we would have.
But you thought we were weak
and you compromised everyone's life.
You were the one who was weak, Dad.
I am not weak.
I am sorry I am not like you.
I won't make the same mistake.
Come with me.
What? Hey!
What?
-Rajesh?
-Dad, what are you...
What are you doing?
What is wrong?
What?
Hi, Alex,
Gautam here from Indian Embassy.
Morning, Gautam.
How can I help you?
The thing is,
I have an Indian lad over here,
who has lost his passport
and papers in Paris,
and he urgently needs to get
to London for a family wedding.
Does he have a UK visa?
Yes, of course, of course.
He has a valid visa.
Let me do one thing,
I'll send you all his details
and why don't you have a look?
His name is Ajit Nagarkar.
But the thing is
he needs to be there tomorrow.
Isn't that a short notice?
Yeah, that is.
But I'll take his direct
responsibility, you know.
I'm really sorry to saddle you
with this.
I'll see what I can do.
Leave it with me.
Thank you so much, Alex.
It's on me, yeah.
-Bye now.
-Cheers.
Why are you trying
to destroy your career?
What if you get caught?
It will be a diplomatic mess.
You will be imprisoned.
You will lose everything
you've achieved so far.
You can lose everything.
I cannot lose more than
what I have already lost.
This boy travelled 6,000 kilometres
to meet that girl because he loves her.
And I couldn't even walk 40 feet
to get you back into my life.
If not my own,
I can at least set right
someone else's life.
I am going to London.
I'll come back in two days
and get you out of here.
Until then,
you should stay away from them.
How will you go to London?
My friend in the embassy,
Gautam, will help me.
Forget about UK and London.
You should come to India with me.
I cannot tell you
how happy my mom will be.
She will get a daughter-in-law
and another son.
Take care of yourself.
Which boy are you
talking about, Rajesh?
I don't understand.
I just don't understand.
Who is he?
Who are you talking about?
Uncle, let me talk to her.
She will listen to me.
Let me try at least.
Why don't you all
tell me about anything?
What the hell is wrong
with you, man, Kartika?
Have you lost your mind?
I don't believe this.
You know how worried
your parents are?
Here, have some pizza.
Come on.
You think I feel like
having a pizza right now?
Look, I cannot tolerate
this gloomy face of yours anymore.
So, please have a slice.
Don't do any drama.
Sheena, please, just let me be.
It's your favourite flavour.
4G Virgin.
Ta-da!
What?
Jaggi and his guardian angel
want to talk to you.
They contacted me on Insta.
Take it.
Come on.
Full drama you are, no?
Oh, I am the drama queen now?
I see.
Where are you, my love?
Hi, I am sorry. I know you've been
trying my phone. I am sorry.
It's okay.
Are you all right?
Don't ask.
I feel like the Bollywood heroines
of the '90s.
Don't worry.
I wanted to tell you that I'll come there,
so you don't have to worry. Okay?
Why are you coming here?
I'll come there.
You are not going anywhere, Jaggi.
I am coming there, please.
I mean I am catching
a flight and coming there.
In a legit manner.
Gautam has sorted out everything.
-Your parents--
-They are happy.
Their only daughter's wedding
getting cancelled is not a big deal.
The wedding
isn't getting cancelled.
Just the bridegroom
is getting an upgrade.
Listen...
I came here
all the way from India, right?
I'll soon be in London.
You know
I had a very difficult journey.
But everything felt fine
whenever I thought about you.
But you...
You have your mom, your dad,
cousins, relatives and
the cancelled groom there.
I too will soon be there.
Kartika, I know, the ten steps
that you'll take towards me
will be much more difficult than
the 10,000 steps I took to get here.
So, if you want to drop out,
it's okay. I mean...
I won't feel bad. I will go back.
Then why did you do so much drama?
To tell you that you are
my number one, my everything.
Can I ask something, Jaggi?
Of course, you can.
Why me?
Why not?
I love you.
I crossed the world
to tell you that.
You know, the things you told me
that take place after marriage.
You told me like
it's a horror story.
Trust me, it won't be like that.
I won't let that happen.
Because we won't get "settled"
after we get married.
We'll have a torrid affair.
Kartika, I don't care if your waist
competes with the IMAX screen.
You'll turn 60, your face will full
of wrinkles and you'll get grumpy,
but you'll still be just
as beautiful to me as you are now,
because you are you.
Why did you come so far?
Why are you crying?
Hello, listen? One second.
You...
Do you have a window close by?
Yes.
Look outside.
Okay.
Can you see the moon?
-No.
-I can't either.
We are made for each other.
I love you.
Love you.
-Let's go.
-You're coming with me?
Of course. You had said you'd offer
me imported liquor at your wedding.
Forgot already?
Bro...
You are rock solid, man.
Jaggi, listen...
We won't be sitting
together in the plane.
You shouldn't come and talk to me.
I won't.
Get serious, Jaggi.
If someone asks--
Then I am a student.
I study physics at the university.
I am going to London
for my cousin's wedding.
Why do you have temporary
travel documents?
Because my passport
got pickpocketed at Metro.
Listen?
Keep this.
You'll take better care of it
than I will.
You will, won't you?
Excuse me?
Yes?
I think you should hear him out.
He has to say something.
What's going on?
Tell her what you just told me.
Get me out of here.
I need a place to stay.
I need a job.
I will give you
all the information.
But please help me out.
What did he just say?
So, now you can send them in.
Hello?
Yeah, thank you.
Oh, my God.
[speaking French]
You have to let the authorities know
that he can't get on the plane.
You have his picture.
You have to stop Gautam.
Stop! Wait!
Have you gone insane, Gautam?
You're trying to smuggle
an alien into the UK.
What have you done, sir?
What have I done?
I have no idea what
you guys are talking about.
I am alone, Marfatia.
I am alone.
They know everything, sir.
-What do they know?
-Where is Jaggi?
-I am not buying it.
Find the boy.
He needs to be somewhere.
We have nothing.
We'll let him board the flight.
Thank you, officer.
It's a huge mistake.
May I?
The plane isn't going
anywhere, Gautam.
Not till we find
and locate this illegal.
I need security to make
a thorough check of the airport.
Let him board the flight.
-Excuse me?
-Yes?
It's too late.
Why they are taking so much time?
Please bear with us, sir.
This won't take too long.
Plane has been thoroughly checked.
Cargo hold, everywhere.
I'm afraid we can't hold it up
much longer,
or else we'll have everyone
disembarked.
We better take our seats.
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen.
This is your captain speaking.
I'd like to welcome you aboard
flight 89B to London.
What were you saying
about your cousin?
He told me that it gets colder
as the plane gains altitude.
Your blood too starts freezing.
You feel as if your limbs
will just break and fall apart.
You cannot breathe.
Your brain stops working.
You cannot even cry
because your tears will freeze.
Yes, the journey does
become easier if you faint.
But you should get up
before the plane lands, or else...
Or else?
"Unite us, Lord"
"I pray a hundred times each day"
"Do the math
Count all the prayers"
-"How can you make a mistake?"
-Sir, can you take me to this address?
Thank you.
"There is a white rooster
On the parapet for you"
"Hey, girl dressed in blue
This boy is crazy about you"
"I'm seeing you
After such a long time"
"I don't want this day to end"
"I just want some place
In your heart"
"That's where I want to dwell"
"I want to keep my head
On your shoulder"
"I want to forget all my sorrows"
"Do the math
Count all the blessings"
"Fate has been sealed"
"One lucky girl
Is going to get married"
"Fate has been sealed"
"One lucky girl
Is going to get married"
Ladies and gentlemen,
prepare for landing.
Cabin crew, please take
your positions for landing.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we are starting our descent.
Please make sure your seatbacks
are in the upright position.
And that your tables
and trays are safely folded away.
Please ensure that your seatbelts
are securely fastened
and all carry-on luggage is stored
in the overhead lockers. Thank you.
This was his bag.
Sir, we've found his belongings.
And this ring.
-I cannot do this.
-Let me talk to her.
-You don't know what this is about.
-Dad, I've decided.
I can speak to my family.
It will be fine.
I can't. I'm so sorry. I...
-Listen, Kartika, we all have a past.
-No, I can't, I...
Okay, look, Kartika,
we can sort it out, whatever it is.
Where do you, I... I am...
Look, I completely understand,
but...
Look, we all have a past, okay?
And it's completely fine.
It's okay for you... Kartika!
Kartika, Gautam.
Where's Jaggi? I've been waiting...
I've been waiting for him.
Where is he?
He...
he bought this dress for you.
Okay.
I...
Where is he? I spoke to him
last night. He must've told you.
He was supposed to come.
We were coming here,
but on the way...
he met with an accident
and he could not make it.
I am sorry.
I'm...
I just told you I spoke to him...
last night.
Love, for some, is a whirlpool
that drowns you,
For some, it is a storm,
a blizzard, a blaze.
Whereas, for some, it is a boat
that takes them to the shore.
For some, it is silence, poetry...
a cool breeze.
There are some who can go
against the world for their love.
And there are some who
keep fighting themselves.
There are some who can travel
a great distance for love,
just like our Jaggi,
and there are some who find it
difficult to even take a few steps.
What is love?
We all have our own way
of expressing it.
We all have our own stories.
There is just one common factor,
and Jaggi became an example of that.
Passion.
Guys, we cannot be so sad
if we are celebrating Jaggi.
Right? Come on, please. It's Jaggi.
No matter if we feel like
"Humpty Dumpty had a great fall,"
we'll always sing a cheerful song.
"Yamma, yamma
Yamma, yamma"
"Such a beautiful atmosphere"
"Yamma, yamma
Yamma, yamma"
Come on! Get up, guys!
-Come on, get up.
-"Such a beautiful atmosphere"
Get up!
"I'm still here"
"Close to you"
"Feel my presence"
"I dwell"
"In your smile"
"I'm helping you discover yourself"
"If you ever want to meet me
Just look at yourself"
"Just tell yourself
What you want to tell me"
"Say all the things
Left unsaid between us"
"Tell me everything in detail"
"I want to make you my passion"
"I am not breathing anymore"
"But I'll stay alive"
"I was, I am and I will be yours"
"You are the one I worship"
"You are my passion"
"Don't forget to reread my letters"
"Smile when you feel overwhelmed"
"All the memories you have of me"
"Make them your passion"
"I want make you my god"
"So that I can worship you"
"I pray for your companionship"
"So that I seek support from you"
"I want to pray and ask for you"
"I want you engraved in my heart"
"I want you to be a habit
I can never let go of"
"I want to make you my passion"
"I want to make you my fate
I want you to be my love"
"I want you to be
My heartfelt prayer"
"I want you to be a habit
I can never let go of"
"I want to make you my passion"
"Why are we bound by limitations?"
"Why are we restricted
By boundaries?"
"Why do we have
So much distance between us?"
"When our destination is the same"
"Why are our paths not the same?"
"I want to set an example for love"
"I want to pen our love story
On water"
"I want you to be
A resounding inkling"
"I want to make you my passion"
"I want you to dwell in my heart"
"I want to stay wordless
And make you my smile"
"I want you to be
A blessing from God"
"I want to make you my passion"